Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5217
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Montgomery County Board of Education [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Monumental Life Insurance Co. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Mor Flo Industries, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Morgan Millwork Co. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- National Car Rental Systems (Box 9, Folder 9)
- National Gypsum Co. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- National Rolling Mills (Box 9, Folder 11)
- New Castle County (Box 9, Folder 12)
- New York Telephone Co. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- News American (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Norfolk Southern Railway Co. (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Norfolk & Western Railway Co. (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Olin Mathieson Chemical Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Olin Mathieson Chemical Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Owens Illinois, Forest Products Div. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Owens Illinois, Forest Products Div. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 20)
- PPG Industries (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Pan American World Airways, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Pennsylvania Liquor Control Bd. (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Pennsylvania Power and Light Co (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Co. [1 of 5] (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Co. [2 of 5] (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Co. [3 of 5] (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Co. [4 of 5] (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Co. [5 of 5] (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Pennsylvania Truck Lines, Inc. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Truck Lines, Inc. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Pepsi-Cola Bottling Co. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Gas Works [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Gas Works [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Gear Corp. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Gear Corp. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Prince George County Police Dept. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Prince George County Police Dept. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Prince George County Police Dept. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Prince William Hospital Corp. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Printing Industries of Washington DC (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Provident Hospital (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Publicker Industries, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Purolator Armed, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Radio Corp. of America (RCA) [folder 1 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Radio Corp. of America (RCA) [folder 2 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Radio Corp. of America (RCA) [folder 3 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Reading Railroad Co. (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Reisch Trucking Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Reisch Trucking Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Resorts International Casino Hotel (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Reynolds Metals, Inc. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Reynolds Metals, Inc. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Rollins Outdoor Advertising (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Ropes Eastern Corp. (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Roubin-Janerio, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Rudy's Farm Co. (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Ryder Truck Lines (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Safeway Stores, Inc. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Safeway Stores, Inc. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Safeway Trails, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Schuster Experess, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Simkins Industries (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Singer Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Singer Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Smith Transfer Co. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Smith Transfer Co. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Southern Pacific Co. (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Southern Railway Co. (Box 11, Folder 12)
- St. Joe Container Corp., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- St. Louis and Southwestern Railway Co. [folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- St. Louis and Southwestern Railway Co. [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- St. Mary County Board of Education [folder 1 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 16)
- St. Mary County Board of Education [folder 2 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 17)
- St. Mary County Board of Education [folder 3 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 18)
- St. Mary County Board of Education [folder 4 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Texas International Airlines (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Union Boiler Co. (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Union Carbide Corp. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Union Carbide Corp. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 1 of 14] (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 2 of 14] (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 3 of 14] (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 4 of 14] (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 5 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 6 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 7 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 8 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 9 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 10 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 11 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 12 of 14] (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 13 of 14] (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Union Pacific RR Co. [folder 14 of 14] (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Federal Aviation Science and Technology Association (FASTA) (Box 13, Folder 3)
- US Alcohol, Firearms and Tobacco, Bur. Of (Box 13, Folder 4)
- US Army: Aberdeen Proving Ground Command (Box 13, Folder 5)
- US Army: Material Development and Readiness Command (Box 13, Folder 6)
- US Civil Rights, Commission on (Box 13, Folder 7)
- US Commerce, Dept. of (Box 13, Folder 8)
- US Defense, Dept. of [folder 1 of 5] (Box 13, Folder 9)
- US Defense, Dept. of [folder 2 of 5] (Box 13, Folder 10)
- US Defense, Dept. of [folder 3 of 5] (Box 13, Folder 11)
- US Defense, Dept. of [folder 4 of 5] (Box 14, Folder 1)
- US Defense, Dept. of [folder 5 of 5] (Box 14, Folder 2)
- US Government Printing Office [folder 1 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 3)
- US Government Printing Office [folder 2 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 4)
- US Government Printing Office [folder 3 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 5)
- US Government Printing Office [folder 4 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 6)
- US Government Printing Office [folder 5 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 7)
- US Government Printing Office [folder 6 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 8)
- US Health and Human Services, Dept. of (Box 14, Folder 9)
- US Labor, Dept. of (Box 14, Folder 10)
- US Library of Congress [folder 1 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 11)
- US Library of Congress [folder 2 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 12)
- US Library of Congress [folder 3 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 13)
- US Marine Corps. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- US National Labor Relations Bd. (Box 14, Folder 15)
- U.S. Navy: Air Rework Facility (Box 15, Folder 1)
- U.S. Navy: Air Station Oceana (Box 15, Folder 2)
- U.S. Navy: Exchange (Box 15, Folder 3)
- U.S. Navy: Norfolk Shipyard [folder 1 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 4)
- U.S. Navy: Norfolk Shipyard [folder 2 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 5)
- U.S. Navy: Norfolk Shipyard [folder 3 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 6)
- U.S. Navy: Norfolk Shipyard [folder 4 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 7)
- U.S. Navy: Norfolk Shipyard [folder 5 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 8)
- U.S. Navy: Norfolk Shipyard [folder 6 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 9)
- U.S. Navy: Ordinance Station (Box 15, Folder 10)
- U.S Park Police (Box 15, Folder 11)
- U.S. Patent & Trademark Office [folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 12)
- U.S. Patent & Trademark Office [folder 2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 13)
- U.S. Small Business Administration (Box 15, Folder 14)
- U.S. Social Security Administration [folder 1 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 15)
- U.S. Social Security Administration [folder 2 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 16)
- U.S. Social Security Administration [folder 3 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 17)
- U.S. Veteran's Administrative Medical Center (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Vermont Northern Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Virginia - Pilot Ledger Star (Box 15, Folder 20)
- WDCA-TV (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Washington Gas & Light Company [folder 1 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Washington Gas & Light Company [folder 2 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Washington Gas & Light Company [folder 3 of 3] (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, WJZ-TV [folder 1 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, WJZ-TV [folder 2 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Washington - Baltimore Newspaper Guild (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Washington County Board of Education (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Washington Gas & Light Company (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Washington Hospital Center [folder 1 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Washington Hospital Center [folder2 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Washington Hospital Center [folder 3 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Washington Hospital Center [folder 4 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Washington Hospital Center [folder 5 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Washington Metropolitan Transit Authority [folder 1 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Washington Metropolitan Transit Authority [folder 2 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 13)
- W.D. Byron & Sons, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Western Pacific Railroad Company [folder 1 of 4] (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Western Pacific Railroad Company [folder 2 of 4] (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Western Pacific Railroad Company [folder 3 of 4] (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Western Pacific Railroad Company [folder 4 of 4] (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Western Pennsylvania Water Company (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Winner Distributing Company (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Western Railroad Awards (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Nation Railroad Adjustment Board, Fourth Division Awards [folder 1 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Nation Railroad Adjustment Board, Fourth Division Awards [folder 2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Docket #2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company Vol. I, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company Vol. I [cont.], 1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)